We will move towards the horizon.
We will find infinity for sure.
Let's fight for this blue sea and
let the wind take us far away.
Don't give up.
So I can come back to this moment.
So I can be present right here.
Throw away this drop.
Something you share.
Shut it up.
Do not be so afraid to podcast.
To have a friend right here.
And I will always be here by your side.
To take care of you.
Even in the darkest of times.
I'll try.
Look and breathe it out.
It's alright now.
Cause we are the ones who
are meant to move in love.
We will move to our single horizon.
We will find insanity for sure.
We're a world for our heads.
We will win for sure.
Dreaming on.
We will move towards the horizon.
We will fight however we can.
In order to be the best we will run.
To the top, to the end.
We gotta be the ones that
just keep dreaming on.
I just can't give up now.
I can never stop cause.
I gotta give everything I got to.
Become the greatest of all times.
We will move towards the horizon.
We will find infinite fortunes.
We will step up and we
will leave for sure.
So keep moving on.
Whoa!
Gimme my soup!
Olin!
This is bad!
She's dangerous even without her memories!
Luffy!
Who is this Tower old lady?
You need to keep your
distance from her old man.
That old lady?
He's an emperor.
What? Really?
Master Queen!
Well?
What happened?
Aren't you gonna get up, lizard boy?
Get your hands off me, you hag!
Do you have any idea who I am?
No!
My...
red...
bean... soap!
I...
wait...
long enough for my tree!
Give it to me!
I know it's here!
Now, fuck it over!
Get down, old man!
No!
Udon!
The present is falling apart!
Looks like they made it out alive.
Good. Hey!
You guys okay?
is he still alive stay
with us master queen
hey can you hear me he's
completely unconscious
But as bouncy as 1.3 billion!
How did she knock him
out in just two hits?
Sniff, sniff.
Sniff, sniff, sniff.
Oh, I think that's my Oshiriko I smell.
I'm shocked she took
down a titan like queen.
Her power must be on a whole other level.
So that's big mom.
She's terrifying.
Report to Commander
Kaido immediately. Roger.
The never-opening cell got broken apart!
I have no idea what's in there.
Whatever it was, it's probably dead now.
Chained up for years, then
crushed to death. Damn!
Understood.
I'll report to Onigashima right away, sir.
The aroma of that sweet soup
is dancing through the air.
What's the plan, Warden?
We need some orders here.
Can we shoot?
No, don't!
You want to make her angry?
Any word from the commander yet?
I've got bad news, Warden.
None of our snails are able to
establish a connection anymore.
That means we can't
contact Onigashima, sir.
How did this happen?
It seems that the enemy is
distracted by the turmoil out front.
That Caribou sure is a useful fellow.
Listen here.
We'll cut off their communication.
Once they can't relay any more messages,
they'll be running around like
chickens with their heads cut off.
And we'll have the upper hand.
Trust me, with the way the smells
work here, it'll be a piece of cake.
In case you didn't know, the
Wano smells have a huge weakness.
Their signal strength is pitifully
weak, so they use a unique system.
Instead of sending their
communication straight to each other,
the snails bounce off a boss snail first.
There's one of these guys in each region.
Once it gets a message,
it sends it to other regions that
would normally be out of range.
Oh, I never really pondered it before.
Well, that's because you're a fool.
Anyway, the plan stars me in my ability.
You know what'll happen if I
gobble up Udon's boss snail?
Absolute chaos is what?
I see now.
That way they won't be able
to relay messages, correct?
Ding, ding, we have a winner.
Fortunately for you, I've been making
good use of my time in this prison.
I know all sorts of things, including
where that big snail is located.
Of course, it will you fool now?
Just sit back, relax,
and let me work my magic.
In the meantime, why don't you go and
gather up all the keys, rise old chum?
It won't be long now, Kawamatsu.
I swear I'll set you
free, no matter the cost!
This smell!
There's no mistaking it!
I found my dear suit!
What a rich and sweet sandpiller here.
I can't believe there's
so much of it, too.
It was worth coming all the way out here.
And look. All right.
Warden, sir, I have really bad news.
What is it? I'm busy.
She's about to find out that the
pie has nothing inside of it.
Ugh!
It was empty all along!
Pig Mom is notorious for her love of food!
What's going to happen when
she finds out there's no soup?
No one will be safe from
her unstoppable rage!
She'll kill us all where we stand!
All right, men!
Evacuate immediately!
This is about to become a disaster zone!
It's every man for himself! Run!
Like your lives depend on it!
Who the hell could have
eaten the entire pod?
Big Mom seems really
bummed out, doesn't she?
I can't really blame her, I guess.
I would kill for another
couple bowls myself.
That soup sure was tasty.
Mr.
Straw Hat!
It was you!
You're the one who ate it! What?
Why is everybody looking at me all weird?
Did you even hear yourself just now?
You just admitted that you ate the soup!
I said that out loud!
It was pretty yummy, though.
Wait, you made me say it again!
I think the harm has already been done.
Luffy Toto,
I finally find Luffy, and he's made
himself the center of trouble, of course.
Hey, did I hear you correctly?
Are you the man who ate
all the red bean soup?
Huh?
Sweet scent is all over you.
Oh, great!
Holy crap!
That was a close one.
If we leave the ring, our heads pop off.
You'll pay with your life.
Wait a second.
Give me a chance to
work this out, Big Mom.
Why do I keep hearing that stupid name?
That person is not me.
You're just a rotten soup
stealer. What do you know?
Wait, you don't recognize me?
Oh, yeah.
She probably doesn't realize it's me
because of my samurai disguise, huh?
If this is anything like her
last food fit, it won't end well.
This is bad.
Like, really, really bad.
Did you hear that?
It's beeping at me.
Our lives are in danger.
If she pushes us back
any further, we're dead!
We cannot back down even a single step!
It's so big, I could have shared it!
That poor little town!
I wanted to thank them for being nice!
This is Oshiroko.
Go ahead and try it, Olin.
I wanted to repay them.
They had so little, but they
gave me a stranger so much!
I only wanted to bring them some
of that yummy red bean soup.
Now it's too late for that.
You took the joy away
from those poor people!
Wait, what?
Those aren't hunger pangs!
This is...
Compassion!
She's literally going to
kill us all with kindness!
You didn't leave a drop
It's over.
I gotta try!
Come on!
What?!
They took him off?!
The colors are gone!
See that, old man? I got
him! They're off! Oh, yeah!
Unbelievable!
He did it!
You won't get away that easily!
Well, let's run, old
man! Wait, Mr. Straw Hat.
Just one more thing.
Hold that feeling.
Protect me from Big Mom.
Stop talking crazy! Let's go!
The midst of danger is
when true power blooms.
Get back here!
You sure you want me to train right now?
If I mess this up, then
you're probably gonna die!
I am quite aware.
That's it! You're done!
Come on!
I won't budge!
I can do this!
Just have to do what
Rayleigh did back then!
I'm going to remove your collar now.
Are you ready, young lady?
Whoa, now hold on! Are you crazy? You
can't! It'll explode! Yeah, it's true!
We've seen it happen before!
Stop!
You'll hurt her!
Bad idea!
Very bad idea! Stop him! Please!
It'll be alright.
Just don't flinch.
I'm telling you, just wait.
This is a big mistake.
He set it off.
It's going to blow.
What are we going to do? You.
GAMING!
How'd he do that?
Damn it.
I'm so close.
I was able to do it, but
I still don't understand.
How'd I manage to pull it off?
But I did it without thinking.
I don't even remember
what I did differently
This time you're not getting away
Mr.
Straw Hat that was an incredible
Ryu-O technique you exhibited
quite truthfully It's far
superior to what I can teach you.
That means you have the
potential to stop her
deflect that woman's
preposterously powerful fist!
I believe that you can save our lives.
In fact, I know you can go
and prove me right—do it now!
I'm worried you'll die.
Though, and I'm ready—fine, then it
appears that he's trying to catch your.
catch your Can he?
It's Luffy. He'll deliver.
He always does.
Gotta loosen up, right? Yeah!
My Haki floor!
Bring it on!
Luffy, I don't know!
Please be okay!
Luffy!
How did you think that would blow?
Damn it!
Oh, crap!
Hang in there!
I'll get you out!
I'm sorry I screwed it up!
I used Barrel to shoot
us both just in case. No!
You're still alive after all of that?
Mr.
Straw Hat, I have one
final thing to teach you.
It's about the application of real.
Listen, please.
Hey, don't force yourself.
You see Haki as you call
it coats your outside
it can be used as armor
and also as a weapon.
However, when you push that
power beyond its limits,
your Haki doesn't simply fortify
your strength within a focus;
it can penetrate the enemy's body itself,
effectively destroying
them from the inside.
You have already harnessed this
ability once those steel collars
were destroyed from within—that
was the power of your Haki.
You've proven that you have
the potential within you.
Man the power you've been working so hard
to master has been
inside of you all alone.
alone
You just didn't realize it was there.
Believe in that power and use it.
Say something.
Come on, please.
You'll be fine.
You hear me.
Wake up.
Please.
Don't die. No.
No.
You have some nerve!
of eating that entire
pot of red bean soup?
I'm going to make you say...
Good luck, Mr. Sriant!
You can do it!
Hello?
Still no connection, huh?
Now what?
I heard the boss snail
vanished into thin air.
What was that rumbling?
It's Pitfall!
Damn it, that blast must have
been the furnace in the prison.
Ironworks exploded!
What are we supposed to do?
We can't take her on.
She's an emperor.
Dammit.
We have no chance against
a monster like her.
She managed to completely
destroy Master Queen.
Sir, you're OK.
That old bat's acting
like she owns this place,
but I'm going to show her what happens
when you move in on Kaido's turf.
Stop running, boy!
I have a plan.
But we only get one shot, so listen up.
You're only delaying the inevitable!
Right now, Big Mom is running
around like a wild boar.
she's gonna charge straight
through udon and loop back
around to us you follow set a trap
right Right here! Huh? Mm-hmm.
I'll crush you!
Sir!
Everything has been set in place!
Here she comes right now, Master Queen!
Oh, man, she just won't give up.
Come back here.
It's my red bean cell.
First floor after all?
Yeah! Got her!
Oh, boy!
It's empty!
No fair!
You tricked me!
I swear it wasn't me!
Daddy!
Yeah!
Lighten the dome!
Nice one, sir!
You really showed her who's boss!
Nobody messes with Master Queen.
He just saved the land of Wano!
Mama!
Mama! Mama!
Where are my sweet darling babies?
My head is throbbing.
Hold on, what was I doing again?
Oh...
We were on our way to the land of Wano.
I fell into the sea and was
separated from my children.
It was right after that
damn king interfered.
I recall washing up on the shore.
There was a dingy little town I
visited, and they served me food.
Oshiruko!
Thou no teacher to screw
with a lead reformer!
You know you were a world-class
pain in my ass back there.
Hope it was worth it.
Now eat dirt, witch.
The Moshiro-ko.
We'd better get out of here
while we still can, you guys.
What happened?
I don't quite understand.
Oh, come on. I'll see you up.
That should have knocked her out cold.
Well, hello.
Hello?
You're one of Kaido's minions, aren't you?
Queen, is it?
I'm a Carrot!
I am not sticking around to
find out what she can do!
You have one more chance to answer me!
Where are you hiding it?
The Oshinu call!
Hand that over! Now!
I'm hungry, so hungry.
What does that look?
Your time is up.
What's it gonna be?
This is it.
I'm done for.
What are you waiting for?
Get out the 100 % sea prism
stone cuffs and chains.
We need to lock her up now.
Go, go, go!
Wrapping around her a thousand times.
Go, go, go! Yes, sir!
She's bound, sir! More! More!
You think that's enough to hold her?
We won't be safe until
you double those chains!
Bring me all the animal sedatives
you can scrounge up in pronto!
Our lives are on the line, you morons!
You! Look alive!
Is my ship ready?
Absolutely, sir!
Prepare to evacuate and leave
only the bare minimum of staff!
Everybody else, get on board right away!
Baba Nico, I'm leaving all of Udon
under your control, you hear me?
Uh, yes, sir.
That old bat completely demolished
every damn door in this place.
So listen, as soon as I'm gone, use the
emergency gates to put Udon in Loguetown.
Throw all the prisoners into their cells
and get these grounds back in order.
As you wish, but I am
concerned about one thing, sir.
And we're off!
Haul ass and don't look back!
We're taking the old hack straight
to Commander Kaito's door!
Let's go!
Set sail!
Full speed ahead!
We're on our way to Onigashima!
Momo!
Hey, look!
The gate's closing!
I wish we could help, but we promised
them we would await their return here.
We must have faith in
them and stand our ground.
I'm going!
Are we on complete Loguetown yet?
Yes, sir!
And is our connection restored?
We still don't have communications, sir.
Unfortunately, it seems that
Udon is completely isolated.
We have no way to exchange
messages with the outside.
Damn it!
Perfect.
That means I can do whatever I want.
Too bad Big Mom and Balloon left, or
I could have used him to practice.
Guess you guys will have to do.
Oh, right.
That little pain in the ass is still free.
Hey, dummy.
I've always been free.
You're just like any other prisoner here.
Don't be so cocky.
Sorry, buddy.
This prison's mine now!